export let data = [
  {
    "question": "This is the largest planet in our solar system.",
    "answer": "Jupiter"
  },
  {
    "question": "He is a famous British playwright known for plays like 'Hamlet.'",
    "answer": "Shakespeare"
  },
  {
    "question": "It's a sport played with a puck and sticks on ice.",
    "answer": "Hockey"
  },
  {
    "question": "A period of ten years.",
    "answer": "Decade"
  },
  {
    "question": "A type of bear known for its distinct black and white coloring.",
    "answer": "Panda"
  },
  {
    "question": "A tropical fruit with yellow skin and tart taste.",
    "answer": "Pineapple"
  },
  {
    "question": "Known as man's best friend.",
    "answer": "Dog"
  },
  {
    "question": "A hard gemstone often used in jewelry, thought to be a girl's best friend.",
    "answer": "Diamond"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Roman god of war.",
    "answer": "Mars"
  },
  {
    "question": "This natural disaster involves the shaking of the Earth.",
    "answer": "Earthquake"
  },
  {
    "question": "A large body of saltwater that covers most of the Earth's surface.",
    "answer": "Ocean"
  },
  {
    "question": "A yellow fruit with appealing taste and a peel.",
    "answer": "Banana"
  },
  {
    "question": "The chemical element with the symbol Au.",
    "answer": "Gold"
  },
  {
    "question": "This is an insect known for its ability to produce light.",
    "answer": "Firefly"
  },
  {
    "question": "A professional who prepares and dispenses drugs.",
    "answer": "Pharmacist"
  }
]
